Guys, go on ahead to the mountain!
Beni beklemeden dağa dönün siz!
Boss Shutenmaru!
Shutenmaru-sama!
I have a bad feeling about this.
İçimde kötü bir his var.
He's crazy...
Aklını kaçırmış...
It was over in a flash. Not long enough for him to sober up.
Saniyeler içinde hallediverdiğinden ayılmasına hiç faydası olmadı.
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka-ya!
Lord Kaido!
Kaido-sama!
Oh no!
Olamaz!
Mother!
Anneciğim!
Damn! My house...! My house!
Sikeyim böyle şansı! Evim... Evim gitti!
Father!
Baba!
Gear Third!
Üçüncü Vites!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Elephant Gun!
Fil Silahı!
Lord Kaido is falling from the sky!
Kaido-sama devriliyor!
Who's that?!
O da kim?
Oh! That's the guy who beat Yokozuna Urashima and Boss Holdem!
Yokozuna Urashima ile Holdem-sama'nın hakkından gelen eleman!
Kiku!
Kiku!
I'm here, Sir Kin!
Buradayım Kin-sama!
Kiku! Are you all right?!
Kiku! Bir şeyin yok ya?
Yes.
Yok.
But...
Lakin...
Oden Castle!
Oden Kalesi!
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama!
Please wait!
Bekleyin lütfen!
Why?! We have to make sure he is all right!
Neden bana engel oluyorsun? Derhâl güvenliğini teyit etmeliyim!
If something happens to him...!
Momonosuke-sama'nın başına bir iş gelecek olursa...
I feel the same way!
Kesinlikle aynı fikirdeyiz!
But don't you have someone else to worry about now?!
Fakat dert etmeniz gereken başka biri daha yok mu?
Tsuru...
Tsuru...
He could wake up and continue his rampage at any moment!
Her an kendine gelip tekrar yakıp yıkabilir!
If that happens, Okobore Town will...
O durumda Okobore Kasabası da...
I understand. I'll make my way to Okobore Town.
Anlıyorum, Okobore Kasabası'na gidiyorum.
Kiku, take care of Lord Momonosuke!
Kiku, Momonosuke-sama sana emanet!
Of course!
Tabii!
You're okay! You all somehow got away, right?!
Bir şekilde kaçtınız, değil mi?
Guys?!
Arkadaşlar?!
Madam Speed!
Speed-sama!
Stay with us! What happened?!
Dayanın! Ne oldu size?
I thought she had left town!
Speed-sama yanılmıyorsam kasaba dışına çıkmıştı!
She just fell down from atop Lord Kaido!
Demin Kaido-sama'nın üzerinden düşüverdi!
Madam Speed! Madam Speed!
Speed-sama! Speed-sama!
Who the hell are you?!
Sen de necisin lan?
Hey, it's Horsella!
Hey, Kısrak!
Horsella!
Kısrak!
Madam Speed!
Speed-sama!
You're...
Sen...
Why are you here?!
Burada ne işin var?
Where's Tama?! You got her home, right?!
Tama nerede? Sağ salim evine götürdün, değil mi?
Tell me, Horsella!
Anlatsana, Kısrak!
Viceroy Kaido spotted us on our way there...
Yolda Kaido-sama'ya yakalandık.
I tried to fight...
Dirensem de...
but I couldn't protect...
efendimi...
my master!
koruyamadım!
Where are you going, Speed?!
Nereye gidiyorsun bakayım, Speed?!
Horsella!
Kısrak-chan!
I received a strange report...
Tuhaf bir rapor kulağıma çalındı.
Damn!
Sıçayım!
I should've...
Bizzat...
stayed with her!
evine bırakmalıydım!
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka-ya!
What are you doing?! Let's run!
Ne yaptın oğlum sen? Kaçalım!
Since he's so big, he probably doesn't know what hit him!
Hâlâ devasa formunda olduğundan neyin çarptığını anlamamıştır!
It's not too late yet!
Kaçma şansımız var!
He got Tama.
Tama'yı öldürmüş.
Kin'emon and the others...
Kin'emonlar da...
Your crew and mine...
ikimizin mürettebatı da...
We don't know if they're okay!
sağ mı değil mi bilmiyoruz!
If I kick his ass now...
Şu an hakkından gelirsem...
it'll all be over, right?
tüm mesele çözülür, değil mi?
Kaido!
Kaido!
I'm over here!
Buradayım lan!
You are...
Sen...
Luffy.
Luffy.
The man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
Korsanlar Kralı olacak adamım!
Blast Breath!
Patlayan Nefes!
So you've come...
Demek...
to Wano!
Wano'ya geldin!
Gear Third!
Üçüncü Vites!
Now he's done it!
Cidden yaptı yani!
He's screwed it all up!
Tüm planımızı suya düşürdü!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
I'll never ever forget the taste of the oshiruko soup and the apple that I had today!
Bugün içtiğim çorbayla elmanın tadını hayatım boyunca unutmayacağım!
Elephant Gatling!
Fil Mitralyözü!
I'll send you flying, Kaido!
Seni yere çivileyeceğim, Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Grizzly...
Bozayı...
Magnum!
Magnumu!
Gear Fourth!
Dördüncü Vites!
Boundman!
Sıçrayan Adam!
How dare you...
Yoldaşlarıma...
mess with my friends, you bastard!
ne cüretle el sürersin, adi herif!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Kong Gun!
Kong Silahı!
Double Culverin!
Çifte Culverin!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Kong Organ!
Kong Organ!
Who is that guy?
O da kimin nesi?
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
King Kong Gun!
Kral Kong Silahı!
Thunder Bagua!
Gök Gürültüsü Bagua!
That moron!
Ah şu aptal!
I can't believe it. He's still breathing.
Gözlerime inanamıyorum. Hâlâ nefes alıyor.
I thought so.
Düşündüğüm gibi.
What?
Ne?
I don't know whether it's his indomitable spirit or bravado...
Yılmaz dövüşçü ruhundan mı yoksa kurusıkı mı atıyor bilmiyorum ama...
but he keeps glaring at me.
dik dik bana bakıyor!
He just looks unconscious to me...
Bana baygın gibi geldi.
What kind of king did you say you'd be?
Ne tür bir kral olacağını söylemiştin,
Boy?!
velet?!